Spring, 1549
Nagoya Castle, Owari Domain
Inuchiyo!
Don't overdo my eyebrows!
Fix it!
Katsusaburo.
Make it higher and fuller.
Higher!
Taper the end, idiot.
Kyosuke.
The belt's boring.
The rope.
The rope!
Quickly!
A fake scar on your cheek
would look heroic.
No.
No!
I see...
You're so dashing.
Beautiful, my lord.
Very gallant.
How do I look, huh?
I'd be smitten.
It's so modern.
I've got the shivers.
I could...
do this.
This!
I feel dizzy!
Her knees will give in!
You can have me!
- What's that?
- You can have me.
What is it?
They're here!
Out of my way.
Quite an entrance!
Have a cup of sake,
Your highness Lady No.
No one else knows this, Son.
I'm very ill.
When I leave this world
it'll bring chaos to our domain.
The Viper will see it as an
opportunity to invade.
I have to stop that
while I'm alive.
It is time to negotiate an armistice
between our domains.
Son...
You'll marry his daughter,
Lady No of Mino Domain.
People call her The Viper's daughter
but her mother's from a noble family.
I'm sure she'll make a good
and sensible wife.
The future of Owari Domain
is on your shoulders, Son.
I saw her! As your father said,
she is fine looking!
Who cares if people call her
the Viper's daughter!
I have a hunch that
she's well-endowed!
Inuchiyo!
Calm down.
Sorry.
Keep it down.
Right away!
You're well-endowed too, my lord!
My lady.
Be sure to remember your father's
words at all times.
Sooner or later, your brother
will revolt against me.
That will turn this domain
upside down.
The Tiger next door will take
advantage of that.
My daughter.
Your next husband will be
the son of Lord Owari.
Not a word!
The future of our domain
depends on you.
He's reputed to be
the biggest idiot in Owari
but I'm sure he's educated and
is a good swordsman.
Quiet! Don't say anything!
Please keep your mouth shut.
You're too outspoken about
your beliefs.
Don't speak!
What is it?
The Lady awaits.
My lord!
Let us through.
Good luck, my lord!
Don't be stingy.
Rub my shoulders.
Not like that.
Don't do it so softly...
Ouch!
May I ask why...
Why must I pour your drink
and massage your shoulders and feet?
Because you're my wife.
Are you tired?
Me? No.
You might not be but I'm
tired after a long journey.
A good husband would
pour me a drink and massage
my sore feet.
Only wimps do that.
Being thoughtful is not wimpy.
You're so misguided.
Watch your mouth. I detest women
who don't know their place.
And I detest men who are ignorant.
You haven't learned any manners!
I say the exact same thing to you!
Excuse me?
The way you're dressed,
it's so foolish!
This is...
It's modern,
you country bumpkin!
You have no idea.
You can't even handle liquor,
you're just a kid.
A little kid... It's embarrassing.
I dare you to kill me right here!
My father will be here
with his army.
Then my father and I'll kill him
and invade his domain!
What a joke!
Did you forget that my father
defeated yours?
He was defeated along with his ego.
Your father arranged this marriage
to stop our attacks.
Wrong.
He sent me as part of
his invasion plan.
My father will defeat you soon.
Mark my words.
Really...
It's treason!
Let go!
Damn...
Mr. Hirate.
Is the young lord always so vocal
in these situations?
Inuchiyo.
He's fairly sensitive, sir.
When he's not in control.
Is the Lady... how can I put it?
Is she passionate?
Fairly.
No, that really hurts!
Stop it! It'll snap.
You'll break it!
You're killing me!
Guards!
My lord!
I'm giving him a foot massage.
Do you like it?
You want it stronger?
Don't stand there!
Kill this woman!
Just a moment please!
Let him go, my lady!
This is not right!
Rescue our Lord!
Please don't!
She's wild! I guess she really is
the Viper's assassin!
This is her 3rd marriage.
Her first 2 husbands
died of unknown causes.
The rumors are true.
She killed them.
You'd better stay
clear of her, my lord.
What's that look?
Me, sir? My apologies, my lord.
Like people say,
the firstborn son is a vacuous wimp.
This domain is ours to take!
Don't be so quick!
My lady, listen to me.
When Father gives the order,
I'll kill him in his sleep.
Shut up, would you?
Spring, 1551
Owari Nobuhide's funeral
Are you planning to kill someone?
Let's continue, Heisuke.
Look at this.
I bet your father doesn't have
such a beautiful hawk.
Quite right.
No one's ever seen
such an impressive hawk.
I'll give you some of its prey.
Get your pot ready.
Don't bother.
You've never brought back enough
to share.
What's that?
The truth.
You've never hunted
with a hawk, woman!
That's right, I haven't
because I never had to.
What?
I've spent my entire life on
Mount Inaba with my father.
Falconry is just a game.
I could get that many birds with
a bow and arrow.
Bring my bow and arrow!
What do you intend to do, Lord?
Don't you get it?
This is a scheme.
Killing her would cause an uproar but
if she slipped off a cliff...
She might die...
By accident!
Lord?
Who's the better hunter?
I challenge you.
I accept.
There's one!
Where...?
Lord.
I can see!
Make a noise!
Hit the gong!
Too soon!
The Lady got one!
He let her!
Right, Lord?
I won't talk.
Your timing's off.
Pick it up.
The Lady got another one!
Almost...!
Another one!
The wind.
The wind blew it away.
No! You can't do that, Lord!
That's not funny, Lord.
The Lady got another one!
I don't eat birds.
That bow's useless.
You guys got in my way!
Lord.
What?
Lord!
There's a deer...!
Go around it.
Yes, Lord!
Get the horses ready!
Quickly!
It's mine.
Approach it from the west!
Go from the other side!
Are you hurt?
Get my men!
Now!
I don't need the help of a woman!
There's no time for that!
Grab my hand.
Move! I can save myself.
Don't be a baby!
If you fell, you'd die.
Dying is better
than getting your help.
Oh, really?
Come back and help me!
I can't hang on any longer.
Here.
Hurry up!
Don't tell anyone about this.
No matter what!
Is anything amusing?
The sea.
Huh? What about the sea?
It might be nothing to you
but there's no sea where I come from.
Shipping brings great fortune.
You want to take our ports?
- Yes!
- I won't let you.
I want access to the sea
so I can go beyond it.
What's beyond it?
Foreign lands!
Barbarians.
What would you do there?
I don't know.
What's there?
I just...
I have an urge to go there.
Renovating Kiyosu Castle
It's sturdily built.
Let my father know about any weak spots
so he can seize the castle.
Sadaie, what method of attack
would you use?
Let me see...
My lady.
Kitsuno.
I wanted you to be the
first to know, my lady.
It's embarrassing but...
I'm pregnant with the Lord's baby.
Heavens! Congratulations!
Well done.
I hope it's a healthy boy.
I appreciate your kind words.
What a happy occasion.
Mr. Sadaie!
Is that so?
Hurry!
Sakuma and his men are late!
So be it!
I will get the General's head.
We'll lead the troops!
Get ready, men!
The Lord is here!
Prepare his horse!
The Lord will ride.
Ready, Sanzaemon.
When they arrive, send them our way.
Halt! Halt!
You're going to Mino Domain
with your army?
Yes.
Revoking the armistice would
be a mistake!
If you take on my father
be prepared to lose.
You're mistaken, my lady.
He's right.
Your father and brother
are fighting.
I'll help your father.
Not for you but to keep to
our truce, so move.
I'm coming too.
Don't be a fool!
Messengers!
The enemy has killed...
your father.
Should we go, my lord?
Wait! We'll stand by.
Stand by?
Are you a coward?
Get it back!
That's my homeland!
It's not so easy!
I'll do it then.
Get my horse!
We're leaving, Sadaie!
Stop her from going!
My lady...
My lady!
Don't do it...!
Stay away.
I've completed the duty
that bound me.
That's not all.
I'm the enemy lord's sister.
I'll be used for
political advantage.
I'd rather kill myself.
Your duty now is...
to be my wife!
Keep your eye on her.
My lady...
May 18, 1560
Shibata Gonroku.
I love your beard.
Yes?
What is it?
Suruga Domain took
both Narumi and Kutsukake castles.
Lord Imagawa Yoshimoto himself
leads armies of
45000 soldiers.
45000 soldiers!
By tomorrow he'll have seized
Marune and Washizu forts.
Then he'll come to us!
This is the end. There's no hope...!
Inoko Hyosuke has secured
the evacuation route.
Escape now.
It'll rain heavily tomorrow, my lady.
Now is the time to escape.
There can't be 45000...
My lady!
The Lord is in the meeting
but he's being indecisive.
What chance would he have
against the Imagawa army?
He'd lose, is what.
All he cares about is his appearance.
His retainers will
desert him for sure.
Owari Domain is doomed.
Oh I worry about Owari.
It's not what you think...
I wasn't making fun of the situation!
Don't be upset!
My lady!
You look like
you've been beheaded.
Having your last laugh?
What did you decide on?
I didn't know what to propose.
It is so hopeless?
At the rate my soldiers
are leaving.
One way of stopping the war
is by killing myself now.
What a boring life it's been...
My father used to say...
he'd destroy the Oda clan
then the Matsudaira clan
then the Imagawa clan
before seizing Kyoto.
What a foolish fantasy.
- If I were you...
- What would you do?
I would rather
take on Lord Imagawa single-handedly
than sit here and die.
It's easy to be a woman!
You can fantasize all you want.
A viper can kill an ox
with one bite on a vulnerable spot.
Their army has no vulnerabilities.
They do.
Think how they'd think.
They think their army will never lose.
That's their weakness...
Where are they?
At Kutsukake Castle
on their way to Otaka Castle.
Ambush them at
Washizu and Marune forts.
What nonsense!
They'll get there before us.
I'll pull my soldiers back from the
forts and defend this castle.
Impossible.
You have no reinforcements.
Your soldiers are fleeing so
you'll die if you stay here.
Go on the offensive.
How about we pretend to assemble
at the forts?
Go on.
In the meantime, move the main army...
Engage the enemy at Okehazama,
kill their lord.
What if they didn't come?
That's the risk.
If they did come, how would we
ambush them?
In rain.
Rain?
Tomorrow's rain will be so intense
they won't hear you approach.
Stars are out.
My lady-in-waiting is
never wrong about rain.
I can't bet on that.
You have to.
Our forces are outnumbered...
Keep their spirits high.
Boost their morale!
Empower them with your words!
My words?
With my words...
I call on you!
Give your lives to me!
Charge!
That won't stir up anyone
except you.
How would the Viper do?
Everyone, listen to me carefully.
The Imagawa soldiers are exhausted
after marching all night.
They don't have your vigor.
Heaven will decide who'll win!
Pull back if they come to you.
Move in if they pull back.
Push, pull and rip their
formation apart!
It's as easy as it sounds!
If you're standing when we win,
you bring honor to
your family for generations!
Victory is ours if you want it!
Matasuke.
Don't mention that I was here.
It should appear that the Lord
decided on his own.
Let people know that he did the
Atsumori dance and put on his armor.
They are back!
Men!
Mino Domain is next!
We'll get Mino back!
Mino Fall, 1567
It hasn't changed!
The hills, fields and rivers!
And Inabayama Castle.
I'll change the name though.
Gizan... Giyou... Gifu...
The hill with an expansive view.
I name it Gifu.
This is Gifu Castle.
You're so flashy.
You don't have to live here.
You can have Mount Sagi.
You grew up in that area.
It's yours to use as you desire.
I see.
Now you have Mino Domain
I have no value as a hostage.
You don't have to be the wife of
a man you don't like.
Likewise. You should celebrate being
free of a wife you dislike.
Indeed.
Does this mean divorce?
All you have to do is ask and
I'll see to it.
It's not my claim to make.
You should ask for it.
You ask for it.
You ask.
How stubborn...
Lord!
What is it, Goroza?
Lord Wada wants a secret meeting
with you.
What for?
I suspect that it's about Lord
Ashikaga Yoshiaki's visit to Kyoto.
Lord Ashikaga...?
He hopes to be installed as shogun
and wants your help.
He wants... who?
You, Lord.
Me go to Kyoto with Lord Ashikaga?
He wants to partner with you
to restructure the shogunate.
Lord, I don't think
this will benefit you.
Lord Takeda and Lord Uesugi refused.
He came to you because you're famous
after the Battle of Okehazama.
I advise you not to
be impulsive, Lord.
Only a fool would go for it.
I won't succumb to flattery.
Very wise of you, Lord.
Owari's biggest idiot
might do it.
Be quiet. Don't say
irrelevant things.
Is this a foolish fantasy?
Acquire as much land as we can
and reach for the highest power.
That's what my father and I wanted.
Through you, I can acquire it.
Speed is crucial.
Waste no time in reaching Kyoto.
Before they build blockades.
Build a road!
So we can move in a large army.
There will be enemies to
defeat before we reach Kyoto.
Recruit any enemy soldiers
who surrender.
Making your army larger as you go!
We'd need to have a lot of
money and rice.
Do we?
No, but we'll be with
Ashikaga shogun's clan.
We can confiscate all we want.
Our first obstacle is Lord Azai.
We need him as an ally.
I'll marry off my sister to him.
And we need steel and horses!
Kyoto Fall, 1568
Allow me to be in your presence.
Look at this!
This is a treasure trove!
Suitable for a man
of your status.
You smartass.
Tokichiro.
Look at him.
He works for
the Western missionaries.
I'll be damned!
He'd make a powerful soldier.
I'll hire him.
Show him what's required.
As you wish, Lord.
By the way, Lady No has arrived.
She's here? Let her in.
This way, my lady.
How was the trip?
How did you find Kyoto?
Look at the piles of gifts!
Aristocrats and merchants gave
me these fine artifacts.
Can you see him? He works
for the Westerners...
What happened?
What do you mean?
Your face...
I don't want to seem provincial.
Aren't I elegant?
Yes, you're ele... eleg...
It wasn't me!
Tokichiro laughed first.
You were first, Lord.
- Shut up, monkey!
- I was laughing with you.
Stop it, my lady!
You're making it funnier!
My stomach's killing me!
I'm going home!
Wait a minute!
My stomach hurts...
Are you okay, Lord?
Tokichiro, I have a favor
to ask of you.
Listen, everyone.
I'll be having a private talk with
the Lord and Lady so keep everyone out.
Sadaie, you can go back
to your quarters.
Don't worry, I'll walk with Lady No.
I'll stay here.
Go back.
Lower your eyes.
Hello!
Take your time.
We have what you want.
Want that frog?
How much is it?
It's 500 mon.
Take it.
May I...?
Thank you, sir.
See the westerners?
Westerners!
What a strange dance!
Would you like to try some, sir?
I like it!
- It's candy.
- How much is it?
I'm dizzy.
What's that?
Watch it!
Try some of this candy...
A pickpocket!
Get out of my way!
Kid, stop!
- You stole my candy!
- Wait!
Mokichi.
You're back!
Give me that!
- Give it back!
- What's that?
What a mess...!
How dare you steal from me, kid?
Let go! This belongs to me!
Let's go.
They stink...
Don't be rude!
We should go.
Move.
That hurts!
Forget it.
Don't!
Leave the kid alone!
That's a silly move...
Kill her!
Stay tough, Viper's daughter!
That's mine!
Leave my wife alone!
Up there.
Come on!
In here.
Here.
May 21, 1570
We can almost see the castle!
Hang on!
You can make it back!
Lord Akechi Jubei Mitsuhide
made it back!
Saito Hideomi died in action.
Toda Genzo died in action.
Kokubo Shozaburo and
Koichiro.
Harada Sukeroku also
died in action.
Asano Shokichi and Heisuke
Also Asano Inosuke died.
Why did they have to die?
Azai Nagamasa betrayed us!
How could he stage a mutiny?
I blame Mr. Gonroku.
Takigawa, how dare you!
Order!
The wrath of the warlords is against
you as you approach Kyoto.
I knew it was a bad idea...
And you share that with us now, Niwa?
I'll behead you next time.
Tokichiro and Akechi.
You fought well at the rear.
I appreciate your recognition, Lord!
It's too soon for compliments.
It's time to strike.
I know. We'll reorganize
and leave immediately.
And behead Azai Nagamasa!
I'm back.
Do you feel better?
I'm sorry about the baby...
You'll have another chance.
Another chance?
I'm too old...
to bear another child.
You don't know that.
Aren't you sad to
have lost a child?
I guess you aren't.
You already have many children.
The ones you had with beautiful
Kitsuno and pretty Nabe.
I'm sure you never wanted my child
from the start.
You thought you had enough!
Stop that petty nonsense!
I'm fighting a war.
I lost so many men this time.
I carry on my shoulders
thousands of soldiers' lives
and my people.
A baby is nothing in comparison.
Lord, if I may speak to you directly.
Please forgive her rudeness.
She was euphoric to have
conceived your child.
Every day she sewed baby clothes...
So what?
You could speak to her
in a more heartfelt way, Lord.
Sadaie.
At this time...
I have no heart.
Enryaku-ji Temple, Mount Hiei
Retreat now! Pull out!
That's a loser's mindset!
Do not pull back! Advance!
Burn it down.
Men, women, children...
Kill everyone.
But Lord...
- Women and children...
- Kill them all.
Kill them...
Those monks...
Why do they support that traitor, Azai,
and go against me?
Why do religious leaders
seek political power?
I'll be punished for your sins
if I have to...
so burn every one of them.
I don't think
that's what a decent man
would do...
I haven't been one for a long time.
I am not a man!
I'm King of the Sixth Heaven demons!
Well said, Lord.
You have to be a demon king
to replace the shogun or emperor.
Let me, Akechi Jubei Mitsuhide,
perform this task, Lord.
Do it right.
Excuse us, my lady.
What is it?
We have a favor
we'd like to ask of you.
What brought you?
I don't know about
destroying a Buddhist temple.
Don't be mistaken.
Those ogres eat animal flesh,
sleep with women and kill people!
Even so, killing women and children
will anger many.
I don't care.
You'll antagonize more people.
Then I'll kill them.
Even the shogun is upset
by your deeds.
He's a useless fool.
I'll expel him from Kyoto.
If he opposes me...
I'll kill him.
There must be a smarter way...
But you're the biggest idiot
in Owari.
Yes, I'm not smart enough
to think any other way.
That's pathetic.
I can help you if...
No.
Is Gonroku behind this?
Or Goroza?
They thought I'd listen to you?
The battle between Owari and Mino
was simple...
There's no time for games.
There's no place for you
in our accomplishments.
New Year, 1574
We gather together to wish for
more fortune in the new year.
Your retainers will work tirelessly
to realize Lord Nobunaga's plan
to unify the whole of Japan.
We will be your loyal retainers
forever and ever.
It's time to celebrate!
You'll prosper like
a growing pine tree
You'll prosper like a growing tree
It's time to celebrate!
You know who our lord is?
The best in Japan, next to none
Join me, Lord.
That's enough, monkey!
Next!
It's your turn, Akechi Jubei.
Do your trick.
What have you got?
I'm but a boring man
with no amusing skills.
So I prepared a very special
new year drink.
Bring them!
These are the skulls of
your enemies, gilded with gold leaf.
The skulls of Asakura Yoshikage,
Azai Hisamasa and Nagamasa.
I've never had such
delicious sake, Akechi.
I'm humbled.
Drink up, everyone!
You forgot that you can't drink.
Stand up! You'll catch
a cold out here.
Your face... It's become so scary.
Has anyone killed as many people
as you?
How many wars will you fight?
How many will die?
What's your point?
My lady-in-waiting gave me
dried persimmons.
She and her husband went to
the mountain and found
a persimmon tree.
Her husband ate too many persimmons
and got an upset stomach.
What's your point?
They're a couple!
Many husbands and wives spend
their lives like that.
Why are you telling me that now?
You told me to go to Kyoto.
It was your idea!
There's no turning back.
Until the day the whole of Japan
has peace...
I'll kill until no one
can oppose me!
Until then
I won't be able to sleep soundly.
My foe will kill me
or I'll kill them.
That's the path I've chosen.
Go away.
Go away!
I don't understand it myself.
I only married him
so I could kill him...
like I did with my other husbands.
After my father died,
I used the Lord
to achieve my own ambitions.
As a result he is
on his way to the top.
Everything is as I planned.
So why...?
What's wrong with me?
I'm fretful.
It's become unbearable.
Something's become more important
to you than your ambitions.
My lady.
You've grown to love the Lord.
I...
love him...?
Seeing the man you love
go through struggles
makes you fret, my lady.
But he hates me.
I don't want
to be here anymore.
You want to see me, Lord.
It's beautiful...
but it's a sad song.
I think I finally understand why...
I always wanted to go
to the land beyond the seas.
I wanted to live a different
kind of life.
Where no one knows anything about me.
Free from my name
and my family.
I'd live a different life.
A foolish fantasy.
My lord.
You once said that if I asked you for
a divorce, you'd see to it.
Let me ask you then.
I'd like to
leave you, my lord.
I accept.
I divorce you right here and now.
Do as you wish.
Thank you, Lord.
Find a good husband
and have a good life.
You're good.
She certainly is.
It's nothing.
Nagashino-shitaragahara 1575
Lord!
Woman.
Why do you hast to die?
Don't!
Take me with you.
Take me with you instead!
Come back!
Come back.
Lord, you're awake.
Give it back!
You're exhausted. You hardly slept
for many days.
Ranmaru...
What was everything for...?
I killed any enemy who
challenged me.
I built a castle like
no other in Azuchi.
I achieved so much that even the
Emperor admires me.
Yes, Lord.
What for?
What was it for...?
To unify the whole of Japan.
Lord!
Speak.
Mr. Sadaie has returned.
I'm opening the door.
My lady.
Open the door for the guest please.
Go away!
Why is he here? I don't
want him to see me like this.
Why wasn't I told sooner?
She didn't want to bother you...
Sadaie, you did not treat her
as a husband should.
But Lord, if I may.
I haven't touched her once
in the last seven years.
What?
I gave you an order.
How dare I...
Knowing how deeply the Lady loves you
I wouldn't dare touch her!
Go away!
Don't look at me.
Come with me to Azuchi.
We're not married now...
Enough of that. Just come!
I'll make you better.
I don't need it!
I don't want your pity.
Who brought him here?
My lady.
Look at his face.
Can you see how exhausted
and miserable he is?
Who needs help?
It is he who needs help.
The Lord is asking
for your help, my lady.
Am I right, my lord?
Please...
Please be by my side.
Up there.
Behold! This is the
Azuchi Castle's keep.
It's one of a kind!
See the view. It's like looking
down from heaven.
This is vulgar.
Vulgar?
For all the climbing I had to do!
This is the latest look
from Western architecture...
Only an overexcited kid would
build this!
You're a kid! It's embarrassing!
You don't look so pale.
You and your antics make the blood
rush to my head!
I made an herb garden on
Mount Ibuki.
I grow medicinal herbs from
the thousands of seeds I collected.
There's no sickness
that can't be cured.
This is from a Western herb.
Drink it.
Here...
Go on.
It stinks! Why don't you try it?
Of course it doesn't stink.
See?
Don't concern yourself with me.
You have a lot to do.
But I want to do this.
I know but
no one else can take on
your responsibility.
All my sons are capable.
There's Gonroku, Niwa,
Akechi and Hideyoshi.
Don't worry about me.
Focus on getting better.
Lord.
Lord!
What?
We'll proceed as I proposed
if you are in agreement, Lord?
About what?
About the reception for Lord Tokugawa.
Do as you like.
Lord!
Unifying Japan is a
critical topic...
As if I don't know that!
Lord, how is it that you allowed a
retainer to yawn in that discussion?
Lord Tokugawa is very observant.
If he no longer saw you as a
threat, he'd revolt.
I beseech you.
You must remind everyone that you're
the fearful demon king.
How?
By putting me in charge
of the reception.
What a grand castle!
I might topple over
looking up at the top!
It's like it's competing
with Mount Fuji!
This is delicious.
It's a delicacy for a
countryman from Mikawa.
The fish smells, Akechi Jubei.
Does it, Lord?
Don't eat it, Lord Tokugawa.
It might make you unwell.
I'm sorry...
That's inadequate!
Jubei.
You almost jeopardized
Lord Tokugawa's life.
You fool...
It's inexcusable!
You embarrassed me
in front of everyone!
Who do you think you are?
You'll never
enter this room again!
That was good.
Mmm, this is delicious.
I messed up.
Everyone froze in fear.
It was effective.
Forgive me.
How are you?
Remember this?
We saw foreigners play one in Kyoto.
I took this one.
It's not easy...
You have a better chance.
You learn quickly.
Where are you going?
To Kyoto.
The Shikoku invasion has stalled.
They need me to lead it.
Come with me to Kyoto.
I'll have a tea party
at Honno-ji Temple.
I won't be long.
If these campaigns go well
that'll end the whole thing.
No more
wars for me.
When I return
we'll take the foreigner's ship
to their land.
Where no one knows anything about us.
Free from
our names and family.
That's why...
you must get better.
What is it?
You want this?
This will...
make sure that you return safely.
A good luck charm.
So I'll leap home like a frog?
I won't need this.
Of course I'll return to you.
This
helped me
come back to you.
I challenge you to learn to play
this then.
By the time I return,
learn to play a Western tune.
I accept.
I'll see you.
Honno-ji Temple June 2, 1582
Out of devotion I followed the
lead of the mad king.
But now he's just a man,
not a demon king.
A mere man can't rule
a unified Japan.
My lord.
I'll finish what you started.
Enemy attack!
- We're under attack.
- Who are they?
It is in fact,
Lord Akechi's army.
Akechi Jubei?
Akechi...!
This way!
Women escape from the back!
There's Lord Nobunaga!
Behead him!
Set it on fire!
Hurry!
Burn it!
Lord!
Watch out!
This way!
Get out of my way!
I must return!
Even if I'm dead
I won't let you have my head!
To the back.
Lord!
I must take my own life.
I've returned.
Let's go.
Vamos!
Stay by my side.
My lady?
50 years of life
is nothing but a dream
when compared...
to the lives of
those who dwell in Heaven.
Anyone alive in this world
is bound to perish.
We all perish.
I've always...
I've always loved you.
Takuya Kimura
Haruka Ayase
Hio Miyazawa
Somegoro Ichikawa
Takumi Saitoh
Kinya Kitaohji
Takuma Otoo
Hideaki Ito
Miki Nakatani
Screenplay by Ryota Kosawa
Directed by Keishi Otomo